Can I ask you another question related
to that?
>> Right.
>> How large should the rotating discs be
if I wanted to experiment with
>> All right. It will be up to you. Allow
us to suggest that you begin with what
you term to be 6 in in diameter.
>> Right.
>> And approximately in your terms, 1/4 of
your inch thick.
>> And what kind of power source should I
use to
have them rotate?
>> You may use any type of what you term to
be electric generator to cause the
initial rotation. If you
put a ring of what you term to be
electromagnets around the outside of the
spinning disc, when it reaches a certain
point, in this way you will find it will
begin to energize the magnets and the
magnets will keep the rotation going. It
will reach a certain level. You will be
able in this way to measure the
amplification of the energy and you will
have the beginnings of the understanding
of the creation of that bubble, that
field.
>> 6 in
and 1/2 in thick, right?
>> Quarter. Half an inch will also be all
right.
>> And the electromagnets how big
>> That is up to you.
So that you can get at least 20 around
the disc.
>> Okay, and they should be in a circle,
right? Around
>> Yes.
>> I see. Thank you. And what about the
polar orientation?
>> North top, south bottom.
>> Any uh field strength for those magnets?
>> For the first experiment, it will not
matter very much.
Now, you may also research some of the
literature which already exists.
Explore some of the ideas that have been
undertaken by the individual in your
society you call Nikola Tesla.